{
    "id": "4875e30b15d04a00aa55742ac7f4d90e",
    "title": "Expect, wait and hope | Grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ff00e41c35ff4594b7ef63b8b59938a9",
            "title": "Expect, Wait And Hope",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ………………….. for her till 11 o’clock. Then I went home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "waited",
                        "expected",
                        "hoped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was ..................... that I would win the first prize.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "expecting",
                        "hoping",
                        "waiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am …………………. for John.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "waiting",
                        "hoping",
                        "expecting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………. she’s has got some good news.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "expect",
                        "hope",
                        "wait"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am still ..................... to hear from her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "waiting",
                        "expecting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am ………………….. a phone call from him in the afternoon.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "expecting",
                        "waiting",
                        "hoping"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Sandra is ……………….. a baby.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "waiting",
                        "hoping",
                        "expecting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is hard to ……………….. for things when you are a child.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hope",
                        "wait",
                        "expect"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………. her at five, but she didn’t come.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "expected",
                        "waited",
                        "hoped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………….. them to turn up at eleven o’clock.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "expect",
                        "wait",
                        "hope"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}